<archimate:ArchimateDiagramModel
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Update TSS Order with Employee Details"
    id="d6748dc3-4e2f-4a12-97ea-d1e06e98d433"
    documentation="Part 2 Information completed by TSS:&#xD;&#xA;Section C - Employee Information&#xD;&#xA;15. Job Code: all TSS excluded (non-contract) job codes are unique to TSS and reflect the&#xD;&#xA;employee’s hourly rate&#xD;&#xA;16. Employee Name: The name of the TSS employee who will be working in the assignment&#xD;&#xA;17. Date of Birth: The employee’s date of birth - only indicated here for new hires&#xD;&#xA;18. SIN: the employee’s SIN number&#xD;&#xA;19. Visa number, if applicable with expiration date. Copies of visas are also attached&#xD;&#xA;20. Hourly Rate: The employee’s hourly rate, this does not include their added casual % in lieu&#xD;&#xA;21. Invoice From: Indication if the employee’s salary must be invoiced to any other Health&#xD;&#xA;Authorities, to whom TSS cannot directly charge. This is also used in the Cost Recovery&#xD;&#xA;process&#xD;&#xA;22. Employee ID: The ID number of the employee working in the assignment, this is generated&#xD;&#xA;when the hire is processed in PeopleSoft&#xD;&#xA;23. Eform/Req/Date: The eform number of the hire for the employee. Used for both new and&#xD;&#xA;existing employees as new assignments may require new records. Date is for the date the&#xD;&#xA;eform was submitted&#xD;&#xA;24. Orientation Deadline: The date by which the employee must complete their New Hire&#xD;&#xA;Orientation in order to be paid for it&#xD;&#xA;25. Assignment Details Sent: If we have sent all the assignment details to the employee -&#xD;&#xA;details from Section B.&#xD;&#xA;26. Timekeeping Information Sent: If we have sent the cost center information to the employee&#xD;&#xA;for their timekeeping.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Ability to link orders to job code and description&#xD;&#xA;i) Ability to link Department (cost centre) coding from host manager to the order and to&#xD;&#xA;Workbrain&#xD;&#xA;j) Ability for the host departments coding to connect directly to the employee file so this&#xD;&#xA;flows through to Workbrain, meaning the employee does not need change their coding&#xD;&#xA;when submitting their timesheet on workbrain&#xD;&#xA;k) Ability to change the department coding for each assignment an employee is deployed&#xD;&#xA;to"
    viewpoint="business_process_cooperation"/>
